Hey,new wallet?
新皮夾？
It was time.
也該換了
The old condom ring in the leather just doesn't say "cool" anymore.
保險套圖案的皮夾已經不酷了
Rachel,you just put an empty carton back in the fridge.
瑞秋，你把空紙盒放進冰箱裡
I know, but the garbage was full.
我知道，但是垃圾袋滿了
Have you ever taken out the trash?
你有倒過垃圾嗎？
Since you've lived here?
從你搬來之後？
Well,I thought you liked doing it.
我以為你喜歡倒
-Third door on the left. -Right!
左邊第三個門 好
（垃圾槽）
Hey,Mr. Treeger.
崔格先生
What are you doing?
你在幹什麼？
I'm sorry.
對不起
It's a little old but....
放了一段時間，不過…
You're clogging up the chute I just unclogged.
不是 我才剛通好又被你塞住了
I'm sorry. I don't come in here a lot.
對不起，我不常來
Of course not. You're a little princess.
當然啦，你是小公主嘛
Daddy,buy me a pizza.
爸爸，幫我買披薩
Daddy,buy me a candy factory.
爸爸，幫我買糖果工廠
Daddy,make the cast of Cats sing "Happy Birthday" to me.
爸爸，叫「貓」的演員 幫我唱「生日快樂歌」
You think you can come here...
你以為你可以來這裡
...make a mess and a big man in coveralls will clean it up?
搞得一團亂，反正有人會收？
Think of someone else for a change.
去找別人吧
Okay,I'm sorry.
對不起嘛
God,if you're going to cry about it!
天哪，這樣也要哭
The One With Ballroom Dancing
本集播出：「與郎共舞」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Treeger made you cry?
崔格把你氣哭了？
He said really mean things that were only partly true.
他說了一些很惡劣 又不盡真實的話
I'll teach him a lesson.
我去教訓他
Joey,don't. Let's forget about it.
喬伊，不要，我看還是算了
That's easy for you to say. You weren't almost just killed!
你說得倒容易 差點被殺的又不是你
All right,that's it. School is in session!
夠了，家裡又不是沒大人
Is this a gym card?
天哪，這是健身中心卡嗎？
Oh,yeah,gym member.
沒錯，我是會員
I try to go four times a week, but I've missed...
我盡量1周去四次，但已經…
...the last 1200 times.
一千兩百次沒去了
So why don't you quit?
那你怎麼不退出？
You don't think I've tried?
你以為我沒試過？
You think I like having $50 a month taken from my account?
你以為我喜歡每個月 戶頭被扣50元？
They make you go all the way down there.
他們逼你大老遠跑過去
They use all these phrases and peppiness to confuse you.
用各種課程和效果讓你昏頭
And then they bring out Maria.
然後還叫瑪麗亞出來
-Who is Maria? -Oh,Maria!
誰是瑪麗亞？ 瑪麗亞
You can't say no to her.
她令人無法抗拒
She's like this lycra, spandex-covered,gym treat.
她是穿緊身衣的會員獨享優惠
Do you need me to go with you and hold your hand?
要我陪你去握著你的手嗎？
You're strong enough to face her?
你可以單獨應付她？
Oh,no. You'll have to come.
不是，你得陪我去
Tribbiani. Hold on.
崔比亞尼 等一下
I'll get the plunger.
馬桶又不通了？
You hold on. You made my friend Rachel cry.
你才等一下 你把我朋友瑞秋氣哭了
So you'll go and apologize to her...
馬上去向她道歉
...unless you want me to call the landlord.
否則我就通知房東
And tell him what?
你要說什麼？
Maybe you haven't heard of "not making girls cry."
你沒聽過 男人不該讓女人流淚嗎？
Maybe you haven't heard of the Rent Stabilization Act of 1968.
你沒聽過 1968年租屋安定法案嗎？
I have actually not heard of that.
我還真的沒聽過
Your friends are violating it.
你朋友違反這個法案
I've been nice until now, but I don't need this grief.
我一直很客氣 但我不必受這種罪
I'm telling the landlord...
我要告訴房東
...Monica's illegally subletting her grandmother's place.
摩妮卡非法分租她奶奶的房子
Your friends are out of here,pal.
你朋友得搬出去了
Why don't you tell me something I don't know?
別說一些我不懂的事
Somebody tell me I don't have to work today.
誰能讓我今天不用上班
What's the matter?
怎麼了？
My first massage is this incredibly gorgeous guy.
今天第一個客人是個大帥哥
Every time I see him, I want to...
每次見到他，我就想…
...do things to him I can't charge for.
替他免費服務一下
So do them for free.
那你就做啊
No,it is forbidden.
不行，公司不准
Mrs. Potter fires people for messing around with clients.
跟客人亂來會被波特太太開除
And it's against my oath as a masseuse.
而且也違反我的按摩師誓言
-They make you take an oath? -No,I made myself take one.
你還得發誓？ 是我自己要發的
No fooling around with clients...
不得與客人亂來…
...and always be prepared.
和有備無患
That one's from the Boy Scouts, but it just makes good sense.
後面是童軍守則，不過說得通
Why not give him to someone else?
你怎麼不把他轉給別人？
No,I can handle it. I'm a professional.
不，我可以應付，我很專業
Pheebs,is that a new ankle bracelet?
菲比，那是新腳鏈嗎？
You got a pedicure.
你去修過腳趾甲
Your feet are all dressed up.
你的腳打扮過
That's the only part he can see when he's on the table!
因為他在按摩台上 只看得到你的腳
You're going to do some feet flirting!
你要用腳勾引他
I don't know what you're talking about.
我不知道你們在說什麼
How do you explain the toe ring?
那你幹嘛戴腳趾環？
It's Arabian Princess Day at work. Leave me alone!
今天是阿拉伯公主日，行嗎？ 少囉唆啦
My hero! What happened?
我的英雄！結果怎樣？
I told him no one treats my friends like that.
我說誰也不准欺負我的姐妹
And he better apologize. See you!
他最好上來道歉，先這樣
Wait a minute.
等一下
What did he say?
他怎麼說？
He wouldn't apologize because you're living here illegally.
他說他不要 因為你們兩個違法
Instead,he'll evict you. See you later!
他要趕你們走，再聯絡
-You got us evicted? -I told you not to go down there.
你害我們要被趕走？ 我就叫你不要去找他
He made Rachel cry!
他把瑞秋氣哭了
Rachel always cries!
瑞秋本來就愛哭
That's not true!
你亂講
You go down there, and you suck up to him.
你給我下去拍他的馬屁
You suck like you've never sucked before!
抱大腿學狗叫都行
All right,I'll try.
好啦，我盡量
If I can't,you stay with us till you get settled.
要是沒成功 你們就先來跟我們住
-Go! -All right,all right.
去啦！ 好啦好啦
I'll have to check first, but he'll be cool.
我得先問錢德，不過應該可以
Remember what we talked about. You got to be strong.
記住剛才所說的，要堅定
Now one more time.
再來一次
Don't you want a washboard stomach and rock-hard pecs?
你不想擁有平坦的小腹 和結實的胸肌嗎？
No,I want a flabby gut and saggy man-breasts.
不想，我喜歡啤酒肚和大咪咪
That's good.
很好
I want to quit the gym.
我要退出會員
You want to quit?
你要退出？
I want to quit the gym.
我要退出會員
You do realize you won't have access to our new Swedish spa?
那就不能享用 全新的瑞典SPA喔
I want to quit the gym.
我要退出會員
Dave in the membership office handles quitters.
好，請找會員服務部的戴維
Excuse me. Are you a member?
抱歉，你是會員嗎？
Me?
我？不是
Sorry. Members only.
抱歉，會員才能進去
I want to quit the gym!
我要退出會員
It's okay,man. Be strong.
放心好了，要堅定
Are you a member of any gym?
你有加入任何健身中心嗎？
No,and I'm not going to be. So save your little speech.
我沒有，也不會 別白費唇舌了
Okay,no problem.
好，沒問題
Could you come here?
你來一下
Hi,I'm Maria.
你好，我是瑪麗亞
（舒活之家）
You have really pretty feet.
你的腳很漂亮
These old things?
這些雞爪？
Would you spend time on my sciatic area? It's killing me.
幫我捏一下臀部，快痛死了
You mean....
你是說…
By sciatic,you mean...
你說的臀部是指…
...the towel-covered portion?
毛巾蓋住的部分？
Sure,I can do that.
好，沒問題，因為…
Because the muscles in the sciatic area can get...
臀部的肌肉有時的確會…
...real nice and tight.
緊實有彈性
So tell me,Rick, how did you injure the area?
瑞克，你這裡怎麼會不舒服？
A 16-hour sit-in for Greenpeace.
我為綠色和平組織 靜坐抗議16小時
-Did you just bite me? -No!
你剛才咬我？ 沒有
Please don't kick the girls out. This was my fault.
怎樣？ 別把她們趕走， 是我不好
You want me to kick you guys out instead?
你要我把你們趕走嗎？
You can't. Where would the chick and the duck live?
不行，那小雞小鴨要住哪裡？
You have pets?
你們養寵物？
Those are nicknames.
那是綽號
I'm the "chick," and Chandler's the "duck."
我是小雞，錢德是小鴨
I would've thought it was the other way around.
我會以為是反過來
Come on. Let the girls stay.
拜託啦，讓她們留下來
I'll do whatever you want.
你要我做什麼都行
Really? You'd do anything?
真的？什麼都行？
Yeah,absolutely.
對，沒錯
I got something.
我知道你能做什麼了
What is it?
什麼？
Can you be my dancing partner?
你能當我的舞伴嗎？
That's not prison lingo,is it?
這不是牢裡的黑話吧？
I want to quit the gym.
我要退出會員
Can you honestly tell me that you're 100% satisfied with your body.
你真的不必來這裡增強活力？
Yes,yes. Most of the time.
大部分時候都不用
I mean,sure,I have my bad days,but then I remember what a cute smile I have.
有時心情不好 我會想到我笑起來很可愛
We were voted "Best-equipped Gym in New York" two years running.
我們連續2年被票選為 紐約設備最佳健身中心
-Do you really want to give that up? -Yes,I hate it here.
你真的想放棄？ 對，我討厭這裡
Everything that you have in here is very heavy.
這裡的東西都好重
Really? Okay?
真的？好
You want to make your friend work out alone?
你總不想讓你朋友落單吧？
-What friend? -Your friend Ross. Just joined.
什麼朋友？ 你的朋友羅斯剛加入會員
（中央咖啡館）
His dancing partner?
他的舞伴？
There's this superintendents' dance, "The Super Ball."
對，他們有一個管理員舞會 叫「管舞會」
He wants to impress Marge, this lady super he likes.
他想引起一個女管理員 瑪姬的注意
Why not practice with a girl?
那怎麼不找女生練？
He's too shy.
他不好意思
He's not good enough to dance with girls yet.
他覺得他還沒資格跟女生跳
Yeah,right.
是啊
He almost danced me right down that garbage chute.
他差點害我跳進那個垃圾槽裡
Would you let it go already? You're fine.
別再念了，你又沒事
So did you quit?
你退出了嗎？
I almost did.
差一點
Couldn't leave Ross there without a spotter.
但我不能丟下羅斯不管
Wait,now,so you joined the gym?
所以你加入會員了？
And that's funny,why?
很好笑，為什麼？
I was just,you know, picturing you working out,and....
我只是在想像你在健身和…
Well,that's it.
就這樣
We're doomed.
我們毀了
They'll take $50 a month from our accounts for the rest of our lives.
我們下半輩子 每個月都會被扣50元
What are we gonna do?
我們該怎麼辦？
You could actually go to the gym.
你們可以去健身啊
Or we could go to the bank...
或是去銀行
...close our accounts and cut them off at the source.
結掉戶頭，斷了他們的財路
You're a genius.
你是天才
Oh,man! But then, we won't be bank buddies.
那我們就不能當銀行好兄弟了
Now there's two reasons.
現在又多了一個理由
You guys,remember that cute client I told you about?
記得我說的那個帥哥客人嗎？
I bit him.
我咬了他
-Where? -On the tushy.
咬哪裡？ 屁屁
And that's not against your oath?
這樣不違反你的誓約？
I know, but the moment I touch him...
我知道，對不起嘛 但是一摸到他
...I want to throw out my old oath and take a new,dirty one.
我就想拋開舊誓約 發一個限制級的新誓
Next time,try to distract yourself.
下次你就讓自己分心
Like when I'm doing something exciting...
對，像我如果在做很興奮的事
...and I don't want to get too...
又不想太…
...excited.
...興奮
I try and think of other things. Like sandwiches...
我就會想別的事，像三明治啦
...and baseball...
棒球啦
...and Chandler.
還有…錢德
-Thank you. -Oh,no,thank you.
謝謝你啊 不，謝謝你
All right,I'm here. Let's get this over with.
我來了，咱們速戰速決吧
Okay,well...
好
...just follow my lead.
跟著我的舞步
Don't we need to do some kind of preparation first?
不必先做點準備嗎？
Like get really drunk?
像是喝個爛醉？
Come on. Hey,just put your arms around me.
來，把手環抱著我
I'm sorry.
對不起
No. It's okay. But if I'm Marge...
沒關係，不過如果我是瑪姬
...my breasts are coming out my back.
我的咪咪會被撞到背後去
Forget it! I'm not being any good at this.
算了，我根本不會跳舞
My mom was right.
我媽說得對
I'm just a big potato with arms and legs and a head.
我只是只穿了衣服的大豬公
Come on,man. You're not a potato.
別這樣，你不是豬公
I'm sure as hell not a dancer. It's no use.
總之我不適合跳舞，練也沒用
Marge will never go for me.
瑪姬不會看上我的
Come on,Treeger. Don't say that.
來，別這麼說嘛
You just need more practice.
你只是需要練習
Come on. Let's try it again.
來，再試一次
Plus,it was probably mostly my fault anyway.
而且問題八成是出在我身上
I'm not that comfortable dancing with a
我不太習慣跟一個…
So how goes the dancing? Gay yet?
舞練得怎樣？ 有「同志」情誼了嗎？
You guys owe me bigtime.
你們欠我一個人情
What was that?
那是什麼？
You just did a little dancy thing.
什麼？ 你剛才在跳舞
-No,I didn't. -Yes,you did.
我哪有 你有
-You did a little hop. -You are so enjoying this.
你剛才跳了兩下 你玩得很樂喔
No,I'm not.
我沒有
And it wasn't a hop. It was a pas de bourree.
而且那不是跳，那叫滑走步
You know the words!
你還知道術語
You are so into this!
你真的很投入
Maybe I'm enjoying it a little. I'm getting pretty good at it.
也許有一點吧，我越跳越好
This is so sweet. Joey,our little twinkletoes.
好可愛喔，喬伊小舞伶
This isn't some kind of girly dance.
這可不是什麼娘娘腔的舞
It's like a sport,it's manly.
這是一種運動，很陽剛的
-Show me some "manly" moves. -All right.
來，秀幾個陽剛的舞步 好
I don't know how to lead.
我不會帶舞
Hello.
你好
We'd like to close our accounts.
我們想把戶頭結掉
Close your accounts? Is there a problem?
把戶頭結掉？有什麼問題嗎？
No,we'd just like to close them.
沒有 沒有，我們只是想結掉
Ms. Lambert handles all our closures.
好，終止帳戶由藍伯小姐負責
Would you come over here,please?
請你來一下
Hi,I'm Karen.
我是凱倫
I want to quit the bank!
我要退出這家銀行
Okay. Baseball.
（好，棒球）
Rick playing baseball. He slides into second.
（瑞克打棒球，滑上二壘）
Maybe even his pants come down a little.
（也許褲子可以拉低一點） （不對！）
Okay,sandwiches. Sandwiches.
（好，三明治）
Okay,on a plate.
（三明治在盤子上）
Maybe Rick's pants come down a little.
（瑞克的褲子拉低一點） （不對！）
Chandler.
（錢德）
Okay,Chandler. That's working!
（好，錢德，有用耶）
Chandler's knees.
（錢德的膝蓋）
Chandler's ankles.
（錢德的腳踝）
Chandler's ankle hair.
（錢德的腳踝毛）
Oh,no!
（完了）
Okay,you're all set.
好了
Wow! That was amazing!
真是不可思議
Was that really just an hour?
真的只有1小時嗎？ 對
In really long-hour world.
在1小時超長的世界裡
What?
什麼？
好吧
I have an enormous crush on you.
我很喜歡你
But since you're a client, I can't ask you out...
但你是客人， 我不能約你
...even though you give me the feelings.
就算對你有感覺
I had no idea.
我完全不知道
I can always find another masseuse.
不過我可以找別的按摩師
Really?
真的？
Yeah,really.
真的
What?
怎麼了？
Suddenly I'm very aware I'm naked.
我突然意識到我光著身體
Quiet down.
好，別吵
Mr. Simon's been waiting Oh,my God!
賽門先生等了…天哪
Why wasn't I offered that?
我為什麼沒有？
I'd definitely pay more for that.
我願意多付錢
We have rules here. This is not that kind of place.
菲比，這裡是有規矩的 我們不搞色情
I know,but this isn't how it looks at all...
我知道，但是你完全誤會了
...because Rick is my husband.
因為瑞克是我的丈夫
Oh,really?
是嗎？
You'd better tell his other wife.
你最好告訴他的另一個老婆
She called three times asking where he is.
她已經打三次來查勤了
Yes,I will tell her.
好，我會告訴她
So you didn't leave the bank?
你們沒有結掉戶頭？
And somehow we ended up with a joint checking account.
沒有 而且還一起辦了一個活存帳戶
What will you ever use that for?
你們要那個帳戶幹嘛？
To pay for the gym.
轉帳給健身中心
So I had a great day.
我今天過得真好
Rick and I hit it off. We were making out.
瑞克和我一拍即合，我們親熱
Then my boss walked in and fired me for being a whore.
然後老闆走進來 因為我賣春而開除我
-You got fired? -Oh,my gosh!
你被炒魷魚？ 天哪
It's so weird. I have never been fired from anything.
感覺好怪，我從來沒被開除過
Sweetie.
親愛的
I started walking around, not knowing what to do next.
我開始漫無目的的亂晃
I started asking people on the street if they wanted massages.
還問路上的人要不要按摩
Then these policemen thought I was a whore too.
結果警察也以為我是妓女
It's really been a bad day, whore-wise.
以一個妓女來說今天還真背
Hey,Duck. Is Chick here?
小鴨，小雞在嗎？
Yeah,Bunny Rabbit.
在，兔寶寶？
Ready for our last practice?
要練最後一次了？
We're not getting that spin right because my place is too small.
轉圈還不夠好，我那裡太小了
-Want to use our place? -No,I had another idea.
要去我家嗎？ 不，我有別的主意
We did it!
成功了！
That was incredible!
我知道，太棒了
That was amazing! We totally nailed it!
太精彩了，非常完美 太棒了
Hey,listen. Thanks a lot,Tribbiani.
崔比亞尼，真是謝了
Oh,my God! Look at the time.
糟糕，都幾點了
I got to catch the bus to the ball.
我得趕公車去舞會
Good luck.
好，祝你好運
Unless you want to practice the fox trot. Or the tango?
還是你想練狐步舞？或是探戈
Thanks,but no.
謝謝，不用了
You see,I think I'm ready to dance with girls.
我已經可以跟女生跳了
-Go get them,Treeger. -Right.
好，去迷倒她們吧 好
You want to come? Marge has a friend.
你想去嗎？瑪姬有個朋友
Really?
真的？
You'd dance good with her. She's the same size as me.
你會很習慣，她跟我差不多壯
No,I'm good.
不，不用了
It looks like you've got great experience.
（拉菈與珍按摩院） 看來你很有經驗
Let's see. Reason for leaving last job?
我看看 你為什麼辭去上一份工作？
They thought I was a whore.
他們以為我是妓女
Okay. We'll give you a call if anything comes up.
好，有消息我們會通知你
Great. Thank you very much.
太好了，謝謝你